In Toronto's war
on crime.
the worst offenders
are pursued by the detectives
of the Specialized Criminal
Investigations Unit.
These are their stories.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Barbara. you should've
brought flowers
for her birthday.
I don't need flowers.
I need news.
Detective Michaels.
I can't go on like this.
We've run out of leads.
Find new ones.
Let's go.
Looking good. Ainsley.
Alright.
Love that pose.
Alright. I think we're done.
Stay for a drink?
Thanks. Riley.
but I think I'm just gonna go.
Everything okay?
Sure.
Never gonna be hotter
than I am now. right?
♪ Gonna be the last
girls at the party ♪
♪ Gonna be the last girls
♪ I might need a smoke break
♪ 'Cause you miss out on
the shots that you don't take ♪
Stunning.
The clothes
or the ladies. Craig?
Wendy. there's only one
lady in this room for me.
♪ Everyone's gone home
No open drinks
near the samples!
Hey. Ainsley. is that your name?
The girls have to get ready
for the finale. Help them.
Be helpful.
Hold this.
Are you even
in the right look?!
It's the last flavor.
Tanya. this is not
what I expected!
Hey. ladies?
Eyes on me. please.
Remember what we talked about.
Powerful and fluid.
Let's have some fun.
Mr. Sharpe.
Excuse me.
♪ It's only three. right?
It's only four. right? ♪
♪ It's only five. right?
It's only six. right? ♪
♪ Gonna be the last
girls at the party ♪
♪ No hard feelings
♪ We're not leaving
♪ While you're sleeping ♪
You wish you were out there?
No. I appreciate this job.
But. yeah.
Well. we'll
have lunch on Monday
and we'll talk
about your future.
You can still get me
into the after-party. right?
Oh. my God.
I'm leaving
and you should too.
It's about to become
hunting hour.
The plus one remains.
Oh. uh. sorry.
It's okay.
Let me get you another.
- Are you a designer?
- Cosmetic surgeon.
Mm.
I'm the reason why everyone
here looks so good.
My friend found this online.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You lied to me. You said
it was for your portfolio--
- Get ahold of yourself.
- Take this down!
Hey. I am working right now.
okay? Hey! What are you...
Don't touch her!
Whoa. whoa. Riley.
Let's get back to work.
Right now.
Hey.
I think it's time
to call it a night. okay?
Frank. take care of this?
Come on.
Let's get you out of here.
Help! Help! Help!
Stop. stop!
Wait. wait. wait. stop! Stop!
This is the new
east end hectare.
We started emptying
the trucks into this section
a couple weeks ago
after the old one got full up.
I mean. if she'd been dumped
into the old site.
we never would have seen her.
- Lucky.
- Yeah.
Was thinking I would buy
a lotto ticket on my way home.
Yeah. you guys
got a system in place
for tracking what part
of the city she comes from?
Give me a sec.
I can narrow it down
to within about four blocks.
Thanks.
What is she.
19. 20 years old tops?
Bruising on the throat.
Petechial hemorrhaging
in the eyes.
She was strangled.
New polish. but the nails
have been clipped and cleaned.
Maybe she fought back
and the killer rewarded her
with postmortem manicure.
No trace evidence.
These marks on her body.
they're not bruises.
Stains maybe?
These scrapes.
they didn't bleed.
they were made postmortem.
Maybe the killer dragged her
after she was killed.
A person adjusts their grip
and repositions.
These are deep and continuous.
I'm not sure she was
dumped from that truck.
I think she was dragged
here by a vehicle.
Graff.
Rear axle. another tarp.
That loader
could have dragged her.
Ainsley Scott.
Elmira. Ontario.
She was to turn 19 next week.
So if that isn't exactly
where she was dumped.
does that mean we're looking
at more than just the east end?
If she was dragged
from a different hectare.
She could have been thrown
into any dumpster in the GTA.
Mr. Scott. why did
Ainsley move to Toronto?
Ainsley came to the city
to be famous.
That's all she ever wanted.
Uh. her mother
passed five years ago.
a drunk driver.
She had Ainsley in dance
and acting classes
before her first holy communion.
Lot of good that did her.
"A lot of good that did her."
referring to the sacrament
or the vocation?
Take your pick.
It's hard to shake
that Catholic guilt.
No. I'm lapsed.
Well. obviously.
something's bothering you. sir.
You're evading eye contact.
rubbing your neck
with one hand. nodding.
That's the Holy Trinity
of non-verbal guilt right there.
Are you insinuating that
I have something to do with
my daughter's death?
- No. sir.
I'm insinuating
that you think you did.
Ainsley
called last week...
...excited.
"Daddy. I think
I got my big break."
Said she needed
$700 for headshots.
I told her I didn't have it.
"Maybe your birthday.
sweetheart?"
So she said
she'd find another way.
Is this why
this happened to her.
because she found another way?
Um. did she tell you
what that. uh. big break was?
I didn't wanna jinx it.
Here.
I'll give you a moment.
If Ainsley's body
was dumped here.
she was picked up on Friday.
- Oh.
- Thank you.
I got it. Here.
Sorry. detectives. She wasn't
dumped at her building.
She's only been dead
three days tops.
Well. there's no
collection on Sundays.
so wherever she was dumped.
she was picked up on Monday.
Judging by the way
her larynx was fractured.
the killer most likely used
his elbow or forearm
and put his entire
body weight on top of her
to close her airway.
Vaginal injuries. tearing.
all consistent
with sexual assault.
but an absence of seminal fluid.
The killer wore a condom.
There's residue.
But no DNA.
Now we know that sexual
murders are committed
by one of two kinds of people
with pathological disorders.
Those who kill to hide
the sexual assault
and those who find gratification
in the act of killing itself.
The latter are planners.
Harder to catch.
Explains the condom
and the clipping and cleaning
of the fingernails.
What about those. uh.
those blue marks on her skin?
Results aren't back yet.
Most likely some sort of dye.
Is this the trash from ident?
Yeah.
They appear to be
mostly fabric swatches.
See the light pass through?
There's pilling. It's cheap.
Disperse blue.
A derivative dye often used
in outdoor textiles.
Exactly.
Outdoor blankets. tablecloths.
When. uh. clothing manufacturers
use it to cut costs.
given the right moisture
conditions. it can stain skin.
Huh. Okay. so these swatches
were caught up in the tarp
she was wrapped in.
so what are we thinking?
Dumpster from a fabric store?
Clothing manufacturer.
textile mill.
somewhere that has its trash
collected on Mondays
and no doubt
a. uh. CCTV dead zone.
The killer.
he keeps telling us
that he's smart.
Let's believe him.
Four down. two to go.
There's no security cameras.
This could be it.
Remote. not much traffic.
Call in the ident team?
Before we waste their time.
let's see if we're wasting ours.
Bateman.
Call them in.
We found our dumpster.
The owner of Walsh's
Textile Mill is in France.
He's been there
for the last five months.
Must be nice.
What about an employee?
No. they didn't recognize
Ainsley from the photographs.
They're mostly older women.
new Canadians.
Probably don't wanna get on
the wrong side of the law.
and it doesn't really fit
the profile. does it?
No. our killer took his time.
He's entitled.
Plus.
the land isn't fenced in.
Anyone could have driven
in there and dumped the body.
Anyone who knew there
weren't any security cameras.
Which is why we're looking
into ex-employees
and anyone in the neighborhood
on the sex offender registry.
New visitor.
Blood in the dumpster
from the textile mill
is from our victim
in the landfill.
But that's not
the only DNA I found.
Ainsley might not be
the only victim.
This is where your first
victim would've been
before the load dragged her off.
So. anything from
Walsh's Textile Mill
would have been dumped here.
Yeah. If it's from that
dumpster one month ago
or one year ago.
then it's in this cell.
You sure your dogs can smell
a body through all this trash?
Up to 15 feet.
30 in the water.
Hmm.
We got another one
deeper down!
Most of one. anyway.
This isn't just a crime scene.
It's a graveyard.
Victim number two.
Freya Klein. killed a month ago.
still in possession
of a German driver's license.
Freya was killed
in the same way Ainsley was.
asphyxia with
a fractured larynx.
There's no ID yet
on our Jane Doe.
Her DNA was found in the textile
mill dumpster with the others
and a broken hyoid bone
indicates the same
cause of death.
She must've been
in pretty bad shape
if we needed a computer to
tell us what she looked like.
Yeah. That still places her
body in the landfill
for about a year.
All three
were sexually assaulted.
all three had
their fingernails clipped.
Same MO. same killer.
A year ago.
a month ago. and now.
His offense cycle is speeding up
and we know that. uh.
serial killers refine
their methods over time.
but this guy. no mess. no DNA.
We haven't found his first kill.
Anything else connecting
these three women?
Well. Freya Klein's parents
said she mentioned something
about an ad campaign
and Ainsley just
got new headshots.
Now. Ainsley's headshot.
though. that-that's full body.
That could indicate
fashion model.
Hmm. fashion models do
ad campaigns.
And Jane Doe's got a gap
in her teeth. That's a thing.
Just like supermodel
Lara Stone.
Yeah. and it's fashion week.
Okay. I'm sorry. did I miss
that you're both fashion buffs?
Oh. human beings have been
decorating ourselves
since the beginning of time.
Yeah. it's fascinating.
Do we change our outside to
match what's within or to. uh.
to express it?
What's this?
Little black dress.
This was in Ainsley's purse?
- Yeah.
- Perhaps we hit the runway.
see if they're serving drinks
with swizzle sticks like these.
They were giving these out
in drinks backstage.
opening night.
And we'll be finding them
in the bellies of
our Branzino for decades.
Walk and talk.
Next model!
I have five designers a night.
five nights...
No! No!
Can we try to have a heartbeat?
Excuse me. uh.
do you recognize this woman?
No.
What about her?
Ainsley was a PA
opening night.
Dorian Sharpe's big show.
- Did you hire her?
- No!
Ainsley is what happens
when someone uses their status
to make you hire help
with no experience.
I see. And who of status
imposed Ainsley Scott on you?
The modeling agent.
Senoia Lee.
She's around somewhere.
Check the bar.
This is awful.
Yes. I knew her.
Ainsley wanted me to rep her.
She was. uh. persistent.
I-I just wasn't sure
if I could sell her.
But you went out
on a limb for her.
you got her a job backstage.
Yeah. she reminded me
of me when I was young.
- How so?
- Small town. starry-eyed.
When was the last time
you saw Ainsley?
The party on Saturday night.
After I left.
I heard that she got into.
uh. an altercation with. uh.
photographer named Riley Chan.
I heard it got really ugly.
Does Riley Chan
have a reputation
for having altercations
with young women?
I don't know.
But he did Ainsley's headshots.
Well. Ainsley's dad said
she couldn't afford headshots.
Maybe Riley Chan
has a side hustle?
She attacked me.
I'd just done her headshots.
For free.
Well. they weren't entirely
for free. There was a...
...a price.
- An exchange.
- Tradesies?
Yeah. we found other women
on your Quiet Night page too.
Was it tradesies
with them as well?
I took her photos down.
- Well. we found them.
- No. I mean...
I felt bad. I even went
to Ainsley's place to apologize.
What? An argument broke out.
one thing
leads to another. and--
No. there were cops
at the apartment. so I left.
Well. I hope you have
someone to corroborate that
because as far as we know.
you're the last person
to see Ainsley alive.
Me and a bunch
of other people.
She was drunk.
Dorian Sharpe
kicked her out himself.
Well. you being
such a nice guy.
I bet you walked her out
and got her a cab.
- I was working.
- You got proof?
- Photos from the after-party.
- Well. let's see them.
- Signed an NDA.
- Oh. well. then...
Riley. You're going down
for distributing pornography
without consent.
That's sex offender registry.
Worry about us. not the NDA.
That necklace. She wasn't
wearing that when she was found.
- Who's the guy?
- Frank Maddox.
Cosmetic surgeon to the elite.
He walked her out of the party
and never came back.
Yeah. I was chatting with her.
Until the altercation.
I offered to get her a cab.
but she wanted to walk.
- Where'd you go after that?
- Home. To my wife.
Good boy.
I'm not stupid. The sort
of girls at these things.
it's a child support lottery.
Gosh. all these
poor wealthy men
getting taken advantage of in
VIP rooms all across the nation.
Well. it's the epidemic
of our times.
These Sharpe parties
sure look wild.
Wilder than the ones
the TPD throw at Christmas.
That's how we got wild.
Yeah. no.
we don't get that wild.
These girls know
what they're signing up for
when they walk
through that door.
They're pulling each other's
hair out to get in.
And your wife
is cool with that?
You staying so late at these
parties all by your lonesome?
I met my wife
at a Sharpe party.
- Oh. yeah?
- Years ago.
He flew me down when he had
his place in Honduras.
Introduced me to
a pretty girl from back home.
She was a model.
Oh. so you
and Sharpe are close?
I'm his doctor.
Hmm. an artist with
a Botox brush.
- Sharpe doesn't like aging.
- Oh.
And what else. um. stops aging?
Seriously. I'd like to know.
What do you do for these guys?
Yeah. you do the. uh...
PRP hair regrowth?
Testosterone?
Uh-oh.
looks like we hit a nerve.
What are the side effects
of testosterone treatment?
Aggression. hyper sex drive--
Not at a legal dose.
Right. because if you
were to inject a man
with more than the legal dose
and that man were to. say. uh.
hurt a woman.
that would make you a--
An accomplice.
You ever inject yourself?
As a lark?
- Do I need to call a lawyer?
- No.
That one's on me.
I crossed a line. alright?
Bring it in. I'm sorry.
Yeah. Okay.
So we giving out
hugs now or...
Ainsley fought back.
Why else would the killer
have clipped and cleaned
her fingernails?
There's no scratches
on his face and neck.
and given how
she was pinned down.
the only place she could
reach would be there or--
His back.
and he didn't even wince.
Not once.
Only when I mentioned
the testosterone treatment.
So. who you thinking?
Grandiose sense
of self is a trait
of the power control
serial killer above the rules.
We've been looking
at the players.
might be time to consider
who built the playground.
You're talking
about Dorian Sharpe.
Mm-hmm.
There he is.
Dorian.
I didn't see you
on the schedule.
Yeah. the girls fit me in.
Fashion week's really
doing a number on my energy.
Need a little pick me up.
Sure. we can do
a milligram of B12.
Yeah. B12. that's...
not really what I was thinking.
Well. if you want
to do testosterone.
we're gonna need
to stay below 200.
- Why is that?
- I'm concerned.
About your heart. your liver.
Oh. okay.
Well. I appreciate the concern.
Frank. I really do.
but let's just stick with
the regular dosage. okay?
We can discuss cutting
back another time.
Heard a girl was killed
after your party.
Same girl you asked to leave.
I did. yeah. jeez.
Cops brought me in
to talk about it.
Think you had something
to do with it or...
They didn't say that.
but it's...
...it's how they made me feel.
Frank and his friends party
with part-time babysitters
like a gang
of delusional vampires.
But... Frank is harmless.
Hmm. what about Sharpe?
Is he harmless?
I met Sharpe when I was down
in New York on a shoot.
And did he ever...
No. at uh... 22.
I was a little long
in the tooth for him.
But I heard stories about
the kind of sex he was into.
That it could get... rough.
Are we talking consensual?
You know. we used
to let men tell us that
truly liberated
women were down with...
anything they wanted.
but. uh.
consensual wouldn't be the first
word that comes to mind.
You think Sharpe's
capable of murder?
Uh. Wendy.
Dorian Sharpe has a life
that gives him access
to an unlimited supply
of young women.
When we enable men like that.
they lose perspective.
When we enable him?
Women are his victims.
Detective.
And then it's up to us
to come forward.
Even when that's a very
dangerous thing to do.
We can offer you protection.
We can protect anyone
you connect us to
who corroborates your story.
There is no protection.
Against that kind
of money and power?
You know. I always got
a bad vibe off Sharpe.
but he wasn't dangerous...
until he was
in an expensive suit.
An expensive suit?
What was he wearing before that?
Coveralls. I suppose.
He started out in some
textile mill
in the north end of the city.
Crawled his way off
the factory floor.
Your first job in the industry
is right here in Toronto
at Walsh's Textile Mill.
Was that a tough job? We drove
past it on the way here.
What a dump.
Right.
Well. I wasn't there long.
No. you were poached
by Atelier X.
Off to the Big Apple.
Five years later.
you were creative director.
so why'd you leave?
Atelier stripped my designs of
their most interesting aspects.
so. um. yeah. I left.
Came home.
Started my own empire.
Do you know this woman?
Nope. I don't think so.
No? 'Cause you asked her
to leave your party.
Well. I ask lots of young
ladies to leave my parties.
There's a certain decorum
that I think might have
skipped this generation.
Huh. What about her?
Have you ever seen her before?
Doesn't look like a model.
so. no. I don't think so.
Her name is Freya Klein.
She was also found
in the landfill. you sure?
- Detectives.
- A bead!
What. from a necklace?
Yeah. probably from a dress.
I would imagine. yeah.
Seamstresses aren't
what they used to be. I guess.
Seamstresses. young ladies.
I bet you long for the good
old days down in Honduras.
Your botulism guy. Frank.
he told us that you used to fly
people down there quite a bit
for some pretty wild parties.
Did those women display
appropriate decorum?
He flew Frank down to Honduras
to help set up his stem cell
research center.
- Anti-aging research center.
- That's right. yeah.
Is there a problem with that?
Looking for more beads.
Detective?
No. Buttons.
See. I love buttons
and what would happen
if I pushed that one?
Well. if I push that button
it locks my office door.
so people can't come in
and bother me.
Hmm. so you don't want
people to come in.
Or to get out.
Tell you what. Detective.
I'll wait to push that button
until after you leave.
how's that?
You think that's our killer?
I think we just walked out
of the crime scene.
You found this bead
in Sharpe's office?
- Yeah. we did.
- We believe it matches
the necklace Ainsley Scott
was wearing the night she died.
Well. anyone
with an RBC Cub Card
can buy one of those
on Instagram.
And no CCTV footage
from the night of the murder?
No.
What about
your first kill theory?
What does that timeline tell us?
Uh. 2010. after his career
took off in New York.
Sharpe bought an estate
on Roatan Island in Honduras.
It was fast becoming a. uh.
medical tourism destination
for the wealthy.
In 2013. he funded
an anti-aging lab there
that was doing some pretty
questionable legal things
with stem cells.
Even bragged
to the New Yorker that.
"He discovered
the Fountain of Youth."
But no missing women
in Honduras?
Ah. police say no.
but we're gonna keep digging.
Then in May 2021.
Sharpe leaves New York
and returns to Canada
to go out on his own.
But we haven't found any other
murders that match his MO.
at least. none connected
to fashion--
Wait. wait. I was wrong.
We do have murders
that match his MO?
No. about
when he came back to Canada.
According to this article.
after he left Atelier X.
he leased a building
in Manhattan
for his new headquarters.
In May 2021.
May 2021...
When did he start
his operation in Toronto?
Not until...
August 2021. three months later.
Hmm. So why
the sudden change of plans?
Why'd he cut and run
for the border?
Because she's there.
Our primary victim's
in New York.
These are
the unsolved homicides
in New York City from 2021.
Remove anything
after August 21.
Remove anyone under 16.
Remove all the men.
Remove any females over 30.
And narrow it to.
uh. deaths that occurred
in the month before Sharpe left
his New York City headquarters.
If one of these women
were his first victim.
there's a chance he left DNA.
Detective Sergeant Michaels.
thanks for meeting with us.
Laura was found
on the lower level of the plaza.
We have no idea how she got
there or who she was with.
Were there any parties or
events at the hotel that night.
Detective Michaels?
Uh... yeah.
there was a Bar Mitzvah
and a fashion show reception.
We couldn't find anyone
who remembered seeing her.
Crime scene was a mess.
She had a bloody nose
and a crushed larynx.
Tell us you got DNA.
Male DNA blood sample
coming your way.
Obviously. we have no match.
Look. detectives.
her mother. Barbara.
she's been. uh...
- Yeah.
I'd love to find
this guy for her.
Of course. Detective Michaels.
You'll be our first call.
- Thank you.
- Appreciate it.
Okay. we need a warrant
for Sharpe's DNA.
It's bound to be a match.
To get a DNA warrant
on someone like Sharpe.
you'll need at least one woman
to corroborate Wendy Maddox's
sexual assault implication--
We're gonna be dealing
with fear. intimidation--
Stop. stop. stop.
I have complete faith
that if anyone
can cause
that first domino to fall
it is you guys.
No. I haven't heard that
Sharpe assaults women.
But maybe I wouldn't.
Your clients
wouldn't come to you?
They might be afraid that what
I would do would cost them work.
Like. get him arrested.
Which I would.
Ms. Lee. of all
the models we contacted.
there were three
that we couldn't reach
and they were
all your clients.
Uh. Anna Trident. Joy Williams.
Lucy George?
Becca. remember.
in the fridge. okay?
Not in the bin.
Uh. yes. Anna.
She got cancelled. poor thing.
Uh. Joy. she tragically
took her own life.
And Lucy George.
uh. I haven't heard
from her in ages.
I'm really sorry. detectives.
Should I answer
your call at two?
Rebecca. would you happen
to have an emergency contact
for Lucy George?
I would have that.
Give me a minute.
Lucy wanted to tell the world
what a creep that Sharpe was.
But I warned her against it.
I mean. she was saying
some wild stuff
and I was wondering if she was
hearing stuff right. you know?
Uh. Lucy has pills. but
she doesn't always take them.
Wild things like... what?
Look. Doris. anything
you say might help us.
Oh. Lord. uh...
Stuff like he was
forcing pregnant women
to get rid of their babies.
so he could steal
the fetus' stem cells.
I told her. "Lucy.
you sound crazy as a loon."
And you didn't
want her to speak up?
I wanted her to talk
to a psychiatrist.
But instead she stopped
talking to me.
Said she was going out
to California.
try her luck out there.
You know. get into movies?
I don't have
her Los Angeles phone number.
Keep looking for her on the TV.
but I haven't seen her yet.
Well. she's not on
social media?
No. she shut all that down.
She thought Sharpe
was stalking her.
You know if you find her.
you might want to tell her
her mother would love
to hear from her.
Of course.
Do you have uh. a photo
of Lucy that we could see?
Yeah.
Gap in those crooked old teeth.
Couldn't afford braces.
Wouldn't you know.
it's the look now.
I'll get the kettle.
That's quite the smile...
We've seen that gap before.
Lucy is our Jane Doe.
I'm sorry. Lucy George's
mother is not an eye witness.
Theo...
There's just not enough
for a DNA warrant.
Come on.
the dental records prove
that Lucy George
is our Jane Doe.
Lucy knew what Sharpe
was all about.
She wasn't afraid to talk
and then she's just gone.
It's a credible theory.
but I need this
to be tight. airtight.
This guy has a huge
team of lawyers.
Yeah. but our laws apply
to the rich as well.
We all seem to forget that.
Billionaires get a free pass.
yet over and over again.
we bear witness to the. uh.
horrific misconduct
of unchecked wealth.
That's why
I'm being extra careful.
Which I why
I'm done with careful.
We don't need a DNA warrant
for Sharpe.
- Frankie--
- We need to get this guy.
Frankie. Frankie!
Well. you're about
to be very. very busy.
Cheers.
Roach will talk to your agent
and we'll start booking you.
Hey. kid. Take your break.
Put. That. Down.
Oh. my goodness.
What's. uh. what's
happening here. folks?
Hmm. Detective Graff was just
about to forfeit his career.
Ah. you really should
listen to my lawyer.
That tracks.
Do not spend time alone
with this man.
Tell your friends.
- What do you mean?
- No. no--
- It's alright.
she has a contract.
He likes the invisible ones
that nobody will miss.
The ones with
big dreams and no chance.
but you know what's
gotten me wondering.
is what happened in New York?
Huh?
What pushed you over
the edge to murder?
Did something humiliate you
to make you wanna go further?
Did Laura Johnson reject you?
Tell you that. uh. "You're old
enough to be her dad?"
Or maybe he had some
performance issues.
Is that why you started
taking testosterone?
Whatever it is
that made you snap.
it awoke something
in you. didn't it?
Something dark.
something you liked.
Oh. please. you know you
really didn't need to resort to.
uh. burglary here. detectives.
If you want my DNA.
I'll give it to you.
I don't know
any Laura Johnson
and I have nothing to hide.
- Sharpe. we need to talk.
- I'm listening.
The cops are asking
questions about Ainsley.
Come on.
Sharpe. Get off him.
Sharpe! Get off him!
Hey. what?
- What the hell. man?
- Good job. bro.
Senoia.
you need to stop worrying.
Worrying causes wrinkles.
Look at me.
I feel like a teenager.
you know why?
Because I have nothing
to worry about.
Okay?
I think we should
get down there.
He knows we're coming for him--
It's okay. I just parked
a spin team outside
his headquarters. the second we
get confirmation that the DNA...
What?
It's not a match.
How is that possible?
Blood sample from
the body in New York
didn't match Sharpe's
cheek's swab.
- Come on. you can't be serious.
- I reviewed your evidence.
You have no prosecutable
case at this time.
Theo. everything
points to Sharpe.
Sharpe willingly
gave you a cheek swab
and the DNA did not match
the blood left
at the murder scene that you
claimed was his first kill.
- He did. didn't he?
- Did what?
He gave us a cheek swab.
Willingly.
Handed it right over.
Yeah. Lucy. you in the building?
Okay. can you meet us
in the kitchen ASAP?
Hey. you. uh.
wanna fill me in?
Well. this is gonna
sound a little weird.
but just bear with me.
- I always do.
Doris George's statement.
the fetuses...
...they're full of stem cells.
Yeah. I'm not so
sure how reliable--
Sharpe willingly
gave us his DNA. Why?
Because he knew
it wouldn't match.
Wait. So you're saying
it wasn't Sharpe's DNA
at the crime scene in New York?
Well. it was
his DNA. his blood DNA.
Because Sharpe is a chimera
from great mythology.
The lion and the serpent
together.
two beings in the same body.
Chimeras in humans
refers to somebody
who's had
a stem cell transplant.
Something that Sharpe
was experimenting with
in his fight against aging.
Okay. uh. I'm with you.
Just take it back a little bit.
- Here.
Hmm.
When somebody has
a stem cell transplant.
their DNA is... May I?
Replaced by the donor's DNA.
Take it away. Da Silva.
It's true.
But only the DNA in the blood.
He has two sets of DNA.
the other cell skin or saliva
from a cheek swab won't change.
So...
he gave us his saliva
because he knew
it wouldn't match the blood
found on Laura Johnson
in New York?
Which contained
his donor's DNA.
and that's why he cut
and cleaned their fingernails.
because the skin cells
underneath
would have Sharpe's
original DNA.
Like that lab in Honduras?
He took the stem cells
and change his blood.
We need to find the donor
or the records.
We just gotta prove it.
Uh. you can start
in the hallway. thanks.
Oh. and mix some bleach
into the floor cleaner
for me. Thank you.
That's oddly nostalgic for me.
My mother used to use it to. uh.
keep the neighbor's
pig farm at bay.
You know. we could
have fought the DNA.
Are you kidding me?
And miss all the fun?
I wish I could see the look
on that Detective's face
when he saw the results.
I mean...
Priceless.
- You know.
if I thought
I was gonna live forever.
I'd try to avoid
life in prison. Sharpe.
Well. here's an idea.
why don't you fix it. Roach?
Or don't. whatever. I'm on
a plane in a few hours anyway.
Says here the lab burnt down
nine years ago.
The records were incinerated.
it was arson
and they never solved it.
What about permits?
I mean. he must've detailed
the procedures he'd be doing.
Well. I'm getting the
impression that Honduran law is.
uh. lax to those with means.
Wait a minute.
We got a sexual assault
complaint
against Sharpe from 2012.
but Graff. look who testified
on his behalf
to cross the charge.
I knew she was hiding
something.
You think she knows
what happened at the lab?
I think she knows everything.
Ah. Ms. Lee. thanks for coming.
Hey. would you like
to finish that at all?
The rest of your meal?
Yeah. my eyes
were bigger than my stomach.
It's just I noticed how you
saved that. uh. that salad.
Was a bit of a tell.
My grandfather. he grew up
during the Depression.
he never left anything
on his plate.
Given the way
dentures were back then.
it wasn't a pretty sight.
let me tell you.
No. he knew poor.
Just like you.
Excuse me?
No hint of an accent.
I never thought to look
for you in Honduras.
Hmm.
Oh.
One second. sorry.
It's my partner.
She says there's.
uh. there's a cleaning van
outside Sharpe's office.
I wonder what that's about.
You said you had information
on Lucy George?
Oh. yes. I-I do.
Please. take a seat.
But first. I would. uh. I'd like
to talk to you about. uh.
your home in. uh. Honduras.
or. well. your lack thereof.
Detective.
I don't like your tone.
What about Dorian Sharpe?
You like him?
I mean. he hired you
from off the street.
You were homeless. correct?
Sleeping rough?
- Yes. actually. I was.
At that point in my life.
I was lucky if I could sleep
in a public bathroom.
And then you had
your own bathroom.
Sharpe lifted you out of poverty
and offered you opportunities
beyond your wildest dreams.
How could you say no to him?
To anything he asked.
So when he needed you to. uh.
discredit a woman's sexual
assault allegation--
I told the truth.
That woman was lying.
I understand. You were...
...just a kid
and you cared about him.
And he was more than
just an employer.
He was a savior of sorts.
but that does not
give him the right
to exploit you.
to abuse you.
Detective Graff.
the relationship
that I have with Dorian Sharpe
is purely professional.
It's okay. Senoia.
I know what happened
in Honduras.
Dorian Sharpe's the bad guy
here and for that. I'm sorry.
Does this feel familiar?
What's happening here?
What I just did?
Couple of low blows
and build you back up again.
make you feel safe.
'Cause that's what monsters
like Sharpe do.
They break you down and then
they put you back together.
Okay. I want my lawyer.
Oh. what. uh. Vincent Roach?
Yeah. sure.
Isn't he
on Sharpe's payroll too?
I mean. he's. uh. a paid
servant just like you--
- I'm not a servant.
- Oh. what are you then?
- I'm a survivor.
- No. you're a chimera
just like Sharpe.
except for you. it's...
...part predator. part prey.
It's how you survived.
You needed those young women
to shoulder the burden
of what he was doing to you.
- I did no such thing.
Sure you did.
Oh. you didn't write the menu.
but you served
those women up on a plate.
You fed the beast
and as the world changed.
as women's eyes were opened to
the horrors that waited for them
behind closed doors.
you were the lure Sharpe needed.
A false beacon.
calling vulnerable
young women to their deaths.
- No!
- Laura Johnson.
brutally murdered in New York.
And bingo. you have
your own modelling agency.
Freya Klein. a stranger
to this country.
tossed into a dumpster.
He met Freya
about an ad campaign.
Campaign that. uh. poof.
magically disappeared
along with her.
And. uh. where's Lucy George?
Lucy went
to California--
No. Lucy went into
the landfill!
And it broke her mother's heart
when we identified her remains.
Take a look!
How did you describe
Ainsley Scott again. huh?
Starry-eyed.
reminded you of yourself.
He said he saw spirit in her!
So I drove her to his office.
I was helping her--
- Oh. you were helping her!
You drove her to a meeting.
a go-see
in the middle of the night?
Didn't you find that
a little odd?
Was she scared?
What did you tell her to...
to ease her fears?
To get her to cross
that dark threshold?
Imagine those...
those starry eyes. yeah?
As he pushed his elbow
down onto her throat
and stole her last breath--
Stop it!
Oh. that man.
he loves a pattern.
I didn't know
what he was doing!
You're gonna bring on
the waterworks?
Sure. go ahead. hey.
Okay. there's one for Lucy.
there's one for Laura.
and there's one for Freya.
and boom.
damn it. take them all.
you earned them.
I was helping them.
Were you?
I was helping them...
No. you weren't.
But you can. You can help them.
Right now. I need to know how
Sharpe changed his blood.
It was a stem cell
transplant. wasn't it?
At the lab in Honduras.
Senoia. I need proof.
I need the name of the donor.
- I don't have--
- It's the only way
we can connect Sharpe
to the blood left
on Laura Johnson--
- I can't!
- Why?
- Because!
Because what?
Because the donor died!
He made me
get rid of my baby.
And he... he used to stem cells
to heal himself.
Look. um... I'm sorry.
But you can help
those women now.
You can bring them justice.
You can bring justice
to the women he killed.
Senoia.
your blood is your testimony.
Toronto police. I need you
to stop what you're doing.
Now.
Dorian Sharpe. you're not
going anywhere this time.
Are we really
gonna go through this charade?
Excuse me. I'm late.
How's that feel?
We're gonna need another sample.
Blood this time.
Should be a 50% match
for Senoia.
I updated Detective Michaels
in New York.
Thanks.
Sharpe made his fortune
making women's clothes.
And he used it to steal
their voice.
Well. four of those women
finally got a chance
to say something about it.
difuze
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm